(Raj:)Now I know how
all those army wives feel.
(Howard:)Would you stop?
(Howard:)We're just gonna be on
the other side of campus.
(Raj:)And right here.
(Howard:)You are a deeply silly man.
(Raj:)He is so afraid of his feelings.
(Penny:)Oh, hi.
(Bernadette:)Got a minute?
(Penny:)Yeah, come on in.
(Bernadette:)I just wanted to apologize.
(Bernadette:)I know what you did
was an accident.
(Penny:)Oh, thank you,
and I'm sorry I lied about it.
(Bernadette:)For what it's worth,
you're a great liar.
(Penny:)Oh, that's what Amy said.
(Penny:)So what's going on with
the research project?
(Penny:)Are they gonna
let you run it?
(Bernadette:)Well, my boss said
he hadn't decided yet,
(Bernadette:)so I gently reminded him
that he's an old rich white guy,
(Bernadette:)and I'm a sweet
little pregnant lady
(Bernadette:)who's not afraid to cry
in front of a jury.
(Penny:)You threatened to sue?